have full confidence in chairman Stefan Schmidt.
The situation he is in right now, as we speak,
the rumors of his divorce are the most damaging,
but so far he managed to shut them down and...
Did you see him downstairs?
Who the hell told him, that I'm here?
Do you want ice?
Cheers.
I've missed you.
Did you?
Mmm.
You smell nice.
Did you tell her?
Yes, she knows.
Whet does she know?
She... She knows what she needs to know.
Alright and what's that?
- She knows what she needs to know.
- And what's that?
It sounds like there's something in particular
you want her yo know?
- Yes.
- And what's that?
I would like her to know
that you've found someone new.
She knows what she needs to know Samir, okay?
- Alright.
- Yes.
Just a second!
Hello?
Yes. It's me...
Sure, I'm going to pick it up soon.
What's that?
- Touche my dick!
- I'll pick it up.
Can't you just put it in some plastic bags,
and leave it in the basement?
I'll pick it up.
Leave it in the basement!
Yes.
No, not now! I can't do that right now.
Please, stop!
Fine, let me talk to her then.
Hi darling, hi!
Why are you not asleep?
I promise that when you wake up tomorrow,
it won't be raining anymore.
Sleep tight.
No, you hang up...
You're a good liar.
You think?
Well, I have practiced a lot,
I'm a politician, you know.
It's difficult for her, she's only five.
It's difficult for me too.
Is it?
Is it really that tough on you?
No.
Not right now.
Right now, it's not that tough.
Stop it.
- You can't break free, can you?
- Yes I can.
No you can't.
Then do it!
It should be like this always.
Just you and me.
Yes.
Why can't we just be together then? Always?
Because I'm 48...
And you are...
I don't even know.
I could be your father.
You really couldn't.
I told him everything yesterday.
So now, I don't have anywhere to live.
You told him what?
Everything.
Everything as in everything with me or what?
No. Not "everything".
Relax.
All I said was that
I'm very much in love with a...
Samir, I'm almost 50 years old.
I'm busy at work, we're about to win the election,
I'm in the middle of a divorce.
And you're young
and everything will be alright.
Trust me, once I was young too,
and everything worked out for me just fine.
Listen, we have to take
one day at a time, right?
What is it?
It's clear you don't want to be with me.
Ew...
Last week you said
we could move in together.
I said "Let's find a place
just for the two of us."
Do you really think that means, that I want
to move in together playing happy family or what?
Yes.
You know my political support base, right?
If I suddenly move in together with...
a guy like you, they'll go crazy.
I already cut ties with my family, and I...
But I never asked you to do that,
let's remember that!
You know what, fuck off.
Fuck off...
Are you leaving?
Hey!
Hello!
Are you still down there?
Hey, come up here!
I have something very exciting to tell you!
Yes, hello, is it Gossip Weekly?
Yes, listen, we already had a chat about
Stefan Schmidt getting divorced,
and there's a good reason for that actually...
Let go!
That's it!
You get that?
Where is your mind at?
What the hell are you thinking?
Was it you who called him
and told him to show up here? Is it?
You are just too pathetic, really.
Fuck you!
How the hell would you make anyone believe,
that I'm gay? I'm not!
Everyone knows that I'm just a normal family man,
who loves his daughter, right?
Listen, You will get what
we initially agreed upon, Samir,
and then I never want to see your face again.
Hi Oliver. It's Britt from the venereal clinic.
We've got the results of your blood tests.
call back so we can schedule an appointment.
Hi Sis.
What are you doing?
You called?
You could've just called back.
- Are you hungry?
- No.
- I can make us some breakfast if...
- Oliver, I'm sleeping. Go home.
Has someone been here?
It smells like dude in here.
You smell.
No!
Oliver, seriously, brush your teeth!
Get out!
Oliver, cut it out!
Oliver, seriously!
Give it back it's not funny!
Give it to me!
Fuck you! Fuck you!
- Seriously, I'll kill you with my breasts!
- No! Don't do that!
What the fuck are you doing?
Some of us have work, you know?
I couldn't sleep.
Aw, you couldn't sleep?
Are you coming to my birthday?
- Who's coming?
- It doesn't matter who else is coming.
Are you excited about being a year older?
That's an odd question.
Are you going to have babies soon?
Am I going to have babies?
- I'm going to turn my pussy into a slip-n-slide!
- Cut it out!
Would you take care of me if...
I got ill?
Hi!
Sexy!
If you're going to be late,
please call ahead.
Oliver, wait here and I'll be back
in two seconds, okay?
- Yes.
- Good.
Okay.
We meet again.
Listen. Your tests came back
and they were both negative.
Okay.
Yes. There's nothing there.
I don't understand.
What don't you understand?
Oliver...
You know what? I'm not your mother.
And it's not my job to parent you.
But I want to help, if you're interested?
- I want another.
- Another what?
I want to take another test.
- The tests are fine.
- Then do another.
Just put a needle in my arm.
It'll take two seconds.
That's not necessary.
Hi Oliver.
You came?
- What?
- Nothing.
It's just always interesting to see
how people look in real life.
You look good in clothes, too.
Come in.
When did you test positive?
- Some months ago.
- Okay.
So it still takes some getting used to?
It's fine.
I think I can handle it.
What?
You're just...
Quite young.
I'm old enough, aren't I?
Old enough for what?
That depends on what use
you have have in mind for me?
Okay?
That's not why why I invited you.
Why, then?
You're always online.
I thought it'd be good for you
to be a little social.
And maybe in another
way than you're used to.
Hang on a second.
Slowly. Slowly...
You okay?
Yeah.
Actually...
Can you take off the condom?
There's really no reason
to wear it, is there?
What do you mean?
It makes no difference,
does it?
That's not how this works.
But... isn't it better without if?
It's not coming off,
and that's final.
Okay.
Forget what I said.
Continue.
- I don't think you understand.
- It doesn't matter!
Forget what I said.
Maybe this wasn't such
a good idea.
Oliver.
Oliver. Come back inside.
Hey...
There's no reason to run off.
Come back inside.
Oliver! Hello? Please...
Please pick up.
Oliver, you promised you'd come.
Hey Sis. It's me...
I've lost my keys, so...
could you let me in?
What do you say?
Thanks.
Is that for me?
- What?
- The poster.
Yes.
It's really nice. Thanks.
You thought to make a website...
and sell them.
Is there something you
want to talk about?
No. What would that be?
Don't you have to clean up?
Why... why are you here?
Are you ill?
Oliver, are you ill?
Move.
Fuck you.
It seems like a big show.
Yeah.
It's a pretty important competition.
Are you coming?
A YOUNG MAN'S DANCE
Couple number 67...
Couple number 16...
19 and 23.
That was the Viennese Waltz.
Wasn't your Dad supposed to be here?
Hi.
Are you okay?
Yes, I'm just nervous.
What's that on your neck?
Concentrate.
It's time.
Your going home.
I'm not going home.
Hit me.
Hit me!
What's wrong?
I'm not working out any more.
Hm?
You're not well. Neither of us are.
Goddammit, stop it!
- Will you stop?
- No!
Stop it.
Hand me that.
You need some too?
Smile, dickheads!
Hey stop it!
Hey, Aksel.
Fuck you.
Give it a rest, will you!
Hey, guys.
Simone, do you smoke?
No I don't.
Come on guys, lend me a cig. Anyone?
Lend you?
Man you're in debt!
Come on, just the one!
Peter, here.
Thanks Aksel, you're a true friend.
The creeper's out.
- Who?
- That, what's his name...
Oh, Aleksander?
So, big plans this weekend?
Is he really gay?
Katrine told me.
She knows someone who dates him.
Fag-xander!
I really don't get why anyone...
Aleksander?
FAG
Why don't you just stay over?
- I could cook something for you.
- No, thanks.
Nothing major or anything, I could probably
get my mum to heat some leftovers or something.
Aksel!
I'm not hungry.
Of course you aren't.
Well, mum's on the paleo diet...
But it might just be your thing.
Paleo isn't my thing.
I think it is...
You pretty much fuck that way,
caveman-like.
I know this is...
difficult for you.
But you don't have to lie to your friends.
I can't do it your way.
You're not doing it in any way.
You're just lying to them.
So, you're just going
to crawl out that window again?
It's ridiculous how you still seem to think
they are the ones judging you.
Fuck, Henrik, weren't you a boyscout?
Well, yeah. But in a big city...
Firewood delivery.
Not sure it's needed!
I heard Simone broke up with Jasper?
She cam asking about you, Aksel.
Simone. She's getting
all worked up for you, Aksel.
Yeah, why don't you get in there, Aksel?
You didn't hold back in grade school.
What's up, you afraid of women, now ?
Your willy's out of order?
Was yours ever in use?
What, you're a fag now?
You're disgusting, Peter!
You did not just fucking do that!
Hey.
So, are you coming by later, or?
I have a class, so...
I'll see you.
Aksel, come on.
Just get over there, already.
What?
Hey, Simone.
Come on guys, let's bail.
Aksel.
Come in!
Good to finally meet you.
I met your mother just now.
Aksel, why are you here?
You're right.
I'm here now.
Good morning.
Hungry?
Yeah.
I'll see you.
Hey, Aksel!
Henrik! Henrik, wait!
Aksel, I swear, I didn't see them.
I didn't see them, Aksel, I...
You saw them there!
No, really. I didn't.
You saw!
You saw! You fucking saw!
Aren't you going to school?
Aksel?
Yeah.
We're both going to be late.
Bet they'll all be wondering about us, then.
God, Aksel.
No one cares!
Come here!
BASED ON A TRUE STORY
What the hell are you doing?
Relax.
You're on in 20 minutes.
What the fuck are you laughing about?
I know that I've made you
sad and upset
I know that I said things
I shouldn't have said
Perhaps it was too much to ask
for me to throw myself at you
I give my love away
I was insecure and afraid
I would regret not telling you
the amazing things
you do to me
I've never felt more loved
than I do with you
do with you
The sun rises over the city
I'm on my way home
alone in the night
I've always known
we'd be together
You're the only one for me
What are you
what are you
going to do with me?
Do you dream
Do you dream of me?
Christina?
Go back to sleep.
I told you to go back to sleep.
I just wanted to know how it went.
It went okay.
Is there something wrong?
Just go back to bed, mum.
- Morning.
- Good morning.
Look at those shoes.
Wow, they're amazing.
Do you want some coffee?
Do you?
Shit or get off the pot.
Kristian, you're disgusting.
It stinks.
- Today's Wednesday, you know?
- So what?
- It's bingo day.
- Are you serious?
I like it when you come with me.
You're my angel
Dear mum
You're like sunshine
on a rainy day
Dear mum
Come dance with me
Dance with me
That was amazing!
What was that song?
It's a song I wrote for my mum.
Dear mum
You're my angel
You're like a sunshine
on a rainy day
Dear mum...
85.
71.
20.
51.
Look at that guy.
What the hell are you staring at,
you old bag?
Mummy's little Christina.
You're so good at bingo.
- Yes.
- She needs a little drink.
- I think you've had enough.
- I want a drink.
- A small drink.
- I think you should go to bed.
Just a little drink.
Come on. Come on.
- Good night, mum.
- You're such a sweetheart.
I said good night.
Christina?
I've meet a guy.
A real man.
Good for you, mum.
Come on.
I can tell you're really jealous.
- If you say so. Good night.
- Damn jealous.
I didn't know you were home.
- Did you just take a shower.
- Yes.
- Did you meet Søren in there?
- Yes, I did.
I'm in there naked and then that
old geezer craps all over the place.
- He didn't even wash his hands.
- Stop it.
It's fucking disgusting.
Why don't you come in
and say hello?
I have to put on my makeup first.
Come and say hello first and then put
on your dress and makeup.
Didn't you tell him that I...
I've only just meet him.
- Fuck you!
- Kristian...
Okay, but only for your sake.
I took a long time.
This is Kristian.
This is Søren.
- Hello, Kristian.
- Hello.
I'm sorry,
but I can't shake your hand.
I've got some bad eczema.
It's very contagious.
- All right. Hi, then.
- Hi.
I'm off then.
I have to prepare for tonight.
- For what?
- I have rehearsal with my band.
Wow, are you a rock musician?
- In a way.
- Yes, you are.
I'd love to hear you play.
Well, see you.
And he shat all over the place?
I hate having
another man in the house.
You're so attached to your mum.
Give her some space.
- He's just close with his mum.
- Close? He sticks to her like glue.
- Ciao, Rodney.
- Bye.
- Christina.
I can be there in 20 minutes.
I look forward
to seeing you, too. Bye.
Do you need a lift home?
- I need some fresh hair.
- Fresh air?
It sounds more like a saucy date.
Take this.
- What's that?
- Pepper spray.
- What do I need that for?
- Just take it.
Hey, baby, you look fucking hot.
Do you suck cock or what?
What the fuck? It's a guy.
Why do you look like that?
Do you fuck other guys, you poof?
- Please leave me alone.
- Why do you fucking look like that?
Do you fuck other guys?
What the fuck's your problem?
Easy, easy, easy.
- Enough.
- Stop sucking dick, faggot.
Fucking homo.
Christina?
No!
My baby...
Baby...
Come here, baby.
My baby...
Hi.
What happened to you?
I crashed my bike.
- How about a beer?
- No thanks.
Where's my mum?
She went to the supermarket.
- I have to go get some cigarettes.
- You can have one of mine.
No thanks. I only smoke filter tips.
- What's up?
- Did Søren move in or what?
He didn't have a place to stay,
so I gave him a set of spare keys.
Are you home  for dinner?
I bought cured pork.
- No thanks.
- Don't be do childish.
Do you want me to wear a dress
or be mummy's sweet, little boy?
I'd prefer mummy's sweet, little boy.
- See you.
- Where are you going?
I need yo by some cigarettes.
- He was badly bruised, your son.
- Yes.
- A gang of immigrants beat him up.
- I thought he crashed his bike.
I hope you'll be understanding.
There's something I want to tell you.
- Sure. Go right ahead.
- It's just that...
- I'm not sure if I should tell you.
- Don't you trust me?
Kristian is a transvestite.
What? He's a tranny?
Yes.
That's why they beat him up.
What can you expect if you dress up
in women's clothes like an idiot?
Søren, behave.
How can I behave when sitting
next to a lovely woman like you?
Kristian, dinner's on the table.
It looks great, mum.
Wine?
- Here's to a wonderful evening.
- Cheers.
Do you dare let go?
Do you dare say no?
Do you dare say no and confront
those who disappoint you?
Do you dare show who you are?
Who you are?
What you can do? What you want?
Who you love and care for?
Do you dare to be happy?
Can you honestly say
that you are happy?
Give me one more.
I think you've had enough.
- Why?
- Because you're off your tits.
You should take
better care of yourself.
- What do you mean?
- Aren't you afraid of getting HIV?
- Those people are using you.
- Exactly.
- And I fucking love it.
- You're crazy.
- Let me take you home.
- Would you really do that, sweetie?
Christina. Christina. Wake up.
You're home.
Thank you.
You're a sweetheart, Rodney.
No! Stop, Søren!
No!
Søren, stop it!
- Is everything okay?
- No, we're.
Are you sure? I could just...
We're all right.
- Good morning.
- Did Søren hit you?
- No, of course not.
Where is he?
- He's at work.
- I know he did it.
He can be a bit rough
when he's had too much to drink.
If he touches you again,
I'll kill him.
- Come on.
- I mean it.
Stop it, already.
- So Princess Mary's here.
- What did you say?
I know people like you
find it hard to behave,
but I swear to you, I have a limit.
You don't want to cross it.
"You don't want to cross it."
- Now what?
- Throw out that drunk.
- Why?
- Because he's insane.
What about yourself?
Søren's a good guy.
He's funny and he loves me
and I love him.
How can you say that?
He's nothing but a fucking drunk.
If you can't stand the heat
get out of the kitchen.
Hi, Christina.
I need a place to stay.
Is something wrong?
No.
- You can stay at my place.
- Can't I just sleep here?
Fine, if you tell me what happened.
I'm having problems with my mum.
Christina? Christina?
Good morning.
I made you some coffee.
Thank you.
Listen. You have to make up
with your mum.
LADYBOY CLUB
Thank you.
- How can I help you?
- Three glasses of white wine, please.
- I want to fuck you.
- Fuck off!
- Didn't I tell you to fuck off?
- Shut it, you filthy slag!
- I'm going to fuck you hard!
- Who are you going to fuck?
Eh?
Girls.
Easy now. Easy now!
- Stop. Can't you just throw him out?
- Listen, Christina.
You shouldn't put up with everything.
No! No, Søren! Stop it!
No! Søren!
Stop it! Stop!Let him go!
Stop! You'll kill him!
Open the door, mum!
If you ever touch my mum again,
I'll fucking kill you!
You're fabulous.
Thank you very much.
Our next song is a song
I wrote for my mother.
I know
Life hasn't been easy
With a special boy like me
And I know
what you're suffered through
Far too often
have I made you blue
But like they say
it's never too late
To start over again
Give me a chance
just one more chance
Please let me come home
Dear mum
You're my angel
You're like sunshine
on a rainy day
Dear mum
Come dance with me
Dance with me
It was so beautiful.
You blew them away.
And your mum was there, too.
- Have you made up?
- Yes.
I'm glad to hear it.
- Why do you care about my mum and me?
- Because I care of you.
Why do you care for me?
Because you sing like an angel.
And I just love to look at you.
Fuck you, Rodney.
I mean it.